

christinabarker.com 919-538-5374 linkedin.com/in/christinabaker35/ christina.barker.35@gmail.com

## **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Empathetic and collaborative problem solver with a genuine curiosity to truly understand and help others. As a designer, I always find myself asking *Why*, *How Might We*, and *Does this experience solve the needs of the user?* I am excited to bring my full stack UX skills and unique global perspective to an organization that is poised and moving towards solving global challenges with technology.

## **EXPERIENCE**

DESIGN WORK March 2017 - Current

- Led a 4 person team in designing the digital layout, typography, graphics for a non-profit client
- Designed an online and print advertisement for real estate firm resulting in 400 additional leads
- Created visual designs for a non-profit fundraising event that garnered over \$60K in donations

## NAVICENT HEALTH - MACON, GA Administrative Assistant to VP

September 2009 - September 2011

- Managed \$500K payroll process for 5 Directors and maintained \$20K travel budget for 10 members.
- Coordinated w/12 member IT and L&D team to create an application system that tracked medical staff certifications ensuring data migration and 100% state compliance w/in 3 months
- Coordinated activities with Vendors to ensure a smooth campus visit.
- Revamped filing system by authoring the security and compliance measures to remove sensitive PII, enforced federal compliance, and ensure data accuracy for 2K documents.
- Prepared, recored, typed, and distrubted the minutes of meetings.
- Mainted VP and senior manager's schedule keeping them apprised of priorities

# THYSSENKRUPP ELEVATOR - GRAND RAPIDS, MI September 2008 - March 2009 Accounts Payable, Admin Asst.

- Managed +\$1M payroll process for +30 team of service technicians and construction technicians.
- Responsible for all accounts payable +\$100K.
- Created an application system that tracked all new construction jobs, listing their budget, PO's and information pertinent to each job.
- Performed accounting tasks such as submitting 10- 15 weekly check requests, and expense reports for the office and invoices.
- Coordinated and submitted all construction permits for new builds and remodles.
- Scheduled and tracked service calls, identifying the priority of the calls.

## **PROJECTS**

## CORE | Mobile and Web Application | View at christinabarker.com

Created as a multi-functional cloud storage desktop and iOS app that connects, organizes, and increases productivity for the customer. My role included research, stragegy, branding, wireframes, prototyping, user testing, and prototyping BRIGHT | Mobile and Web Application | Currently in the research phase. Created to be a part of Google Classroom. This Android app will reinforce literacy skills. My role includes research, stragegy, user testing, wireframes, branding, user testing, and prototyping

## **EDUCATION**

#### Bloc

2018 - 2019 Certificate UX Designer

## Southern New Hampshire University

2015 - 2018

BA, Graphic Design 3.5 GPA

## **Macon State University**

2008-2012

**Business Administration** 

## SKILLS

## **TOOLS**

Adobe Creative Suite

Figma

Sketch

Invision

Wire-framing

### RESEARCH

User Interviews
Personas
User Stories
Usability Testing

#### **DESIGN**

Storyboards
Wireframing
Mockups
Prototyping

### **DEVELOPMENT**

Terminal
Git/GitHub
HTML/CSS
JavaScript/jQuery